rendrfx.com 2017-12-11

# Privacy Policy - RendrFX

**RendrFX, Inc.** ("Provider," "we," "us," "our") respects your right to privacy. We are committed to protecting your privacy. Your continued use of our website and your submission of any information to us indicates that you have read, understand and agree to our Privacy Policy.

We have detailed our Privacy Policy so that you know how we collect and protect the information you decide to provide us. This Privacy Policy will tell you:

What information is collected by the Provider.

How we may share information.

How you can let us know your preference for sharing of information.

**WHAT INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT?**

As a visitor to the RendrFX website, you can engage in many activities without providing any Personal Information, but please note that website usage information is automatically collected as defined in the Automatic Information section below. When you order products or services as a RendrFX Buyer or Artist Contributor, we may collect the following Personal Information from you as detailed below.

Depending upon your use of the website, some of the information that we ask you to provide will be mandatory and some will be voluntary. If you do not provide the mandatory data with respect to a particular activity, you will not be able to engage in that activity.

Customer Information

* * *

We receive and may keep information you gave us because you decided to register on one of our websites, or because you decided to fill out any other form on a website of ours. This information may include:

**Your legal name**

**Your e-mail address**

**Your username and password**

**Your mailing address**

**Your month and year of birth**

**Customer Media or Content uploaded by you to the website**

**Billing information such as the number, expiration date, card type, and billing address of your credit card**

**Demographic information such as your job title, job description, company name, and company type.**

Information may also include any other personal information or unique preference information you choose to provide us.

Artist Contributor Information

* * *

We receive and may keep information you gave us because you decided to register on one of our websites, or because you decided to fill out any other form on a website of ours. This information may include:

**Your legal name**

**Your e-mail address**

**Your username and password**

**Your primary address**

**RendrFX will verify your legal name and primary address by asking you to either: a) upload a scan of a government issued ID (which will be stored on our servers); or b) provide a credit card number. Your credit card number will be used solely for the purpose of verifying your name and address. The credit card number will not be stored.**

**Your workplace if working on behalf of another entity.**

**Your month and year of birth**

**Content submitted by you to the website**

**Payment and Artist Contributor information including, but not limited to, your Stripe account information or other Payout method as set forth by RendrFX, payout email, display name, skill level, content focus, etc.**

Information may also include any other personal information or unique preference information you choose to provide us.

Depending upon your use of the website, some of the information that we ask you to provide will be mandatory and some will be voluntary. If you do not provide the mandatory data with respect to a particular activity, you will not be able to engage in that activity.

Updating Your Personal Information and Privacy Preferences

* * *

You have the right to access and correct, or delete certain Personal Information and privacy preferences at any time. This may be accomplished by clicking on the link, "My Account", where you can view and make changes to most of your Personal Information immediately. For security purposes, certain Personal Information can only be changed by contacting support by email.

Children

* * *

We do not intend to solicit or collect Personal Information from anyone under the age of 18. If you are under 18, please do not enter information on this website or engage our services. If you are under 18 and are interested in using any of our services, please have a parental guardian contact us at Support@rendereffects.com. If you believe a child of yours under the age of 18 has entered Personal Information please contact Support@rendereffects.com to have the data removed and terminate the child’s account.

Automatic Information

* * *

We want you to be aware that certain tools exist to help us service and recognize you. For your convenience, to help us personalize your experience or better serve your needs, we may receive and store certain types of information when you visit one of our websites. You may be familiar with the term “cookies”, which are unique alphanumeric identifiers. These cookies are placed on your computer when your web browser accesses our websites. In addition to cookies, we may use log files, transparent images, and/or third party sources to collect information used to educate us on things such as how you navigate to and around our websites, product browsing, content accessing, and purchasing data. We may also use this information to send you more targeted marketing or promotional materials. If you choose, there are utilities available for purchase from independent software providers to install on your computer as well as tools/preferences you can choose through most web browsers to make website visits anonymous. Of course, cookies let you have a more satisfying website experience, so we recommend that you leave them turned on.

**ONCE INFORMATION IS RECEIVED, HOW IS IT SHARED?**

Within the Provider

* * *

We share information we collect from all points of contact within the Provider organization, including with companies that are affiliates of the Provider. The information you give us and information about your transaction may be combined with other personally identifiable information available from our records and other sources.

We store the information that we collect through cookies, log files, transparent images, and/or third party sources to create a summary of your website usage and preferences. We then tie your personally identifiable information, and/or your Account usage history, to information in the summary, in order to provide tailored promotions and marketing offers, to improve the content of the website for you and others, and/or to determine your preferences.

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you with services and access to your requested activities. If you wish to delete your account or request that we no longer use your information to provide you services contact us at Support@rendereffects.com, and we will respond to your request within 30 days. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

Governmental Agencies or Other Companies

* * *

We may share information with governmental agencies or other companies assisting us in fraud prevention or investigation. We may do so when (1) permitted or required by law, or (2) trying to protect against or prevent actual or potential fraud or unauthorized transactions, or (3) investigating fraud that has already taken place. In all cases, this information is not provided to these entities for marketing purposes.

Right to Transfer

* * *

Should the Provider choose to sell or transfer business assets, or to engage in a transaction where it is required to share or transfer your information, it is possible that the information we possess may be transferred as part of that transaction. The Provider may decide to retain a copy of the information post sale or transfer.

Information Sharing with Service Providers / Agents

* * *

RendrFX uses Stripe for payment processing information. Please refer to Stripe’s Privacy Policy and Terms of Service for further information on their policies. RendrFX reserves the right to change payment processing providers as needed.

RendrFX also shares Personal Information with certain companies that perform services on our behalf (including, but not limited to, Firebase for Account information storage and user data, Amazon Web Services and Google for cloud processing and rendering, FilePicker for uploading, processing, and viewing media). We only share the Personal Information which is necessary for these providers to perform those services. Unless we seperately notify your otherwise, we require any company with which we may share Personal Information to limit the use of such Personal Information to the performance of services for RendrFX. We do not sell or otherwise provide Personal Information to other companies for the marketing of their own products or services.

**WHAT HAPPENS IF I HIT A LINK TO ANOTHER SITE FROM A PROVIDER SITE?**

Our websites may offer links to other sites. Other sites have their own terms of use and privacy and security policies. If you choose to visit one of these sites, you should review the policies that govern that particular site.

Application of This Privacy Policy

* * *

This Privacy Policy applies to all information collected or submitted to the Provider. Other affiliated entities of the Provider may obtain information independently from transactions and experiences with you or from other sources. This Privacy Policy does not pertain to that information.

Your Consent

* * *

By sharing information with us, you consent that the Provider can use the information collected or submitted as described in this Privacy Policy. We may change or add to this Privacy Policy so we encourage you to review it periodically.

September 10, 2015  
Version 1.0
